# FELIPE VELASQUEZ ESCOBAR

# JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Colombia

#### **ABOUT ME**

Frontend Developer with experience in JavaScript, React, Django, and REST API consumption. I have knowledge in developing responsive designs using tools like Sass, Bootstrap, Semantic UI, and MUI. I use Git and GitHub for efficient version control. I am currently focusing on strengthening my knowledge in Clean Architecture, Redux, and TypeScript. I am passionate about technology and programming; my goal is to continue learning to become a versatile professional.

# **LANGUAGES**

English - B2 Spanish - Native

## **EDUCATION**

### **HIGH SCHOOL**

Pascal NV. Platform

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM

ParqueSoft.TI

### **REACT & DJANGO COURSE**

Udemy

# **CONTACT ME**



+57 317 282 1594



juanfelipevelasquezescobar82@gmail.com



https://github.com/felipevees



https://portafolio-gilt-five.vercel.app/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/felipevelasquez-escobar-a9a74123b/

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

**ECOMMERCE** 

January 2024 - Present day

Development of requirements and design of a website using Django, JQuery, Bootstrap, and other tools for a sports business, freelance mode.

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER

LANDING PAGE November 2023 - December 2023

Development and design of a website using React, Sass, and other tools for a professional portfolio in freelance mode.

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

LANDING PAGE July 2023 - August 2023

Development and design of a website using React, Bootstrap, Sass, and other tools for a mobile phone company in freelance mode.

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROJECT May 2023 - June 2023

Full-stack development and design of a website using React, Django REST Framework, Bootstrap, Sass, and other tools focused on restaurant clients.

#### **SKILLS**

- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- Redux
- Typescript
- HTML y SCSS
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- GIT and GITHUB
- Django
- DB SQL

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- · Constant and independent learning
- · Work ethics
- Teamwork
- Logical and critical thinking